<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on JC Palmer</title>
    <link>https://jccpalmer.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on JC Palmer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.140.1</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 10:40:15 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jccpalmer.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Proxying Docker containers on a separate VLAN</title>
      <link>https://jccpalmer.com/posts/proxying-docker-containers-on-a-separate-vlan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 10:40:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jccpalmer.com/posts/proxying-docker-containers-on-a-separate-vlan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;d like to start this off by clearly stating that I&amp;rsquo;m not a network engineer, nor do I know how to be one. That said, however, a project idea came to me one day as I thought about breaking myself free from Cloudflare Tunnels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I built a weird setup with a Raspberry Pi, Nginx Proxy Manager, a separate VLAN, and a series of Docker containers that I wanted to access externally. I wasted hours, days, in pure frustration, only to find out that the solution was so simple.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setting up Kobo sync with Calibre Web</title>
      <link>https://jccpalmer.com/posts/setting-up-kobo-sync-with-calibre-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 08:37:18 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jccpalmer.com/posts/setting-up-kobo-sync-with-calibre-web/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There I was, minding my own business downloading ebooks from my Calibre server to my Kobo Libra 2 via the web browser when I stumbled upon a comment. This comment, courtesy of a now unknown Redditor, briefly mentioned something I&amp;rsquo;d never heard of. Apparently, Calibre Web, the very service I used to sideload books onto my Kobo, had a built-in Kobo sync feature.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I stared incredulously at this comment, and then started to do some digging. I even ventured onto Google to find answers, as DuckDuckGo proved unable to pinpoint the exact information I needed. Sure enough, I found what I wanted, or at least the beginnings of it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
